Guide to Jonathan Soffer Papers RG.046
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Jonathan Soffer Papers
1989-2007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Soffer, Jonathan M., 1956-
RG.046
10 Linear Feet
Biographical / Historical
Jonathan Soffer is a professor at NYU Tandon School of Engineering in the Technology, Culture, and Society Department. His work is primarily on Ed Koch and Matthew Ridgway.
Scope and Contents
The Jonathan Soffer Papers contain research documents from 1989 to 2007. These documents were assembled by Soffer during his time researching for books on Ed Koch and Matthew Ridgway. The documents are primarily archival and scholarly research regarding New York politics. Papers contain interview, newspaper clippings, academic article, drafts, and archival research. The collection is 10 linear feet, located on bay 26, shelves 4E, 5E, 6E, 7E, and 7F.
Arrangement
This collection is housed in 10 boxes and arranged into two series and eight sub-series per series. Series: Koch Project, Sub-series: Archival Manuscript Research, Correspondence, Drafts, Interviews, Newspaper Research, Research, Scholarly Articles, and Teaching. This collection was not arranged by the archivists; Jonathan Soffer's original order was kept and only light arranging was done for clarity. His file names were preserved. "Illegible" is noted where words in file names could not be transcribed.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated to the Polytechnic Institute of New York University Archives by Jonathan Soffer in 2021.
Polytechnic Institute of NYU
- Series I: Koch Project
  - Subseries A: Archival Manuscript Research, undated
    - Manuscript from EIK, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Wagner MSS 78-80, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence, 2004-07-18-2007-07-10
    - Letter from Ed Koch July 2007, 2007-07-10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Letter from Ed Koch June 2007, 2007-06-29 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Email Correspondence, 2004-07-18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Drafts
    - Ch 5 txt - 1st draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Chapter 7 Draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Koch Manuscript, 2001-06-21 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Interviews
    - Robert F. Wagner Jr. Interview, 1992-08-18 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1982 Playboy Int, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Lo Cicero Transcript, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Subseries E: Newspaper Research
    - New York Times Search Inquiries, 2001-09-27 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1955-1957, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1955-57 Politics/De sapio, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bohemia Nest 55-7, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1958-1960, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Politics 1958-60/De sapio, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bohemia Culture/1958-60, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1955-57 Background Village/Jane Jacobs Planning - Wash Sq, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1955-7 Misc But of interest/Bios, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1958-60 Wash Sq/Village Planning, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - SPACE Planning & Polit [illegible] 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Planning/Politics General, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Politics and Planning 1963, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Counter Culture, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1961, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Politics 1961, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 1961 Planning/Culture, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - MANA/Community, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - MacDougal Bohemia/Culture 1964 reset speed, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1962, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Cultural Background, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 1962 Koch (Passannante Race), undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Culture, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Koch 1963, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Koch 1964 Politics Elections, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 80063 DiSapio Docs, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Civil Rights 1964 RACE, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Koch 1965 Politics, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Bohemia and Culture 1965 CIVRTS Vietnam, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1966, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Politics, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Viet, Cr, Counterculture, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Space/Zang, etc, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1968, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Congressional 1968, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Koch Council-Politics 67-68, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Scans, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Politics 1981 July-Dec, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Service Delivery 1981 July-Dec, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - July-Dec 1981 Public Space, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Voice Newspaper Scans 1981, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Voice 1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Wayne Barrett and Joe Conason Newspaper, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Fiscal Observer 77 Campaign, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 1982? Newspaper, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Jan-June 1980, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - July-Dec 80, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - AIDS Docs, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Daily News 1977 Aug 1-Dec 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Post/News Dec 77, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Post Aug-Nov 77, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Post Aug-Sept 77, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1980 July-Dec, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Fiscal/Labor 1981 Jan-Dec, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Politics 1981 Jan-June, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Race 1978-1980, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Labor 1979 Jan-June, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - K + International Politics Jan-June 1979, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Fiscal/Labor Jan-June 78, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal Labor July-Dec 1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - July-Dec 1978 Public Space, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Politics 1979 Jan-June, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Politics July 78-Dec 1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Fiscal/Labor 1979 Jan-June, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - HHC Pol/Race Jan-June 79, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1977 [illegible] (Elections), undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Jan-June 78 Politics/Race, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Fiscal Labor 1979 July-Dec, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Politics 1979 July-Dec, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Service Delivery 1979 July-Dec, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Race Politics Bruce Wright Crown Heights HHC, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1979 July-Dec, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Politics 1980 July-Dec, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Jan 1979-June 1981, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Fiscal/Labor 1981 July-Dec, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HHC/Sydenham, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Fiscal/Labor 1980 July/Dec, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Politics 1980 Jan-June, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Labor Economy 1980 June-Dec Tenant Strike, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Education, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Fire, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - HHC and other agencies, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Police/Courts/Prisons, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Transit, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Sanitation, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Civil Serv-Service Delivery Goal, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Welfare, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Cars/Traffic/Bikes, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Convention Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Census, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Crime, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Crown Heights, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Energy Crisis, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Gay Rights Public Space, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Glitz/Nightlife, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Graffiti/Vandalism, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Harlem, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Homelessness, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Housing Gen'l/Tax Liens, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Landmarks, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Loft Conversion, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Misc, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Parks, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Planning, Gen'l Car Budget, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Protests, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Skyscrapers/Midtown, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - S. Bronx, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Stable Nabes Co-Terminality, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Tax Abatement, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Times Sq Sex Industry Gambling, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Underground Economy, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Waterfront/Westway Battery Pk Cty, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Watertunnel/Infrastr Bridges, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Koch Quotes of the Day, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Profile/Special, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Koch Magazine Profiles EK Lindsay Obit, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Misc Mags to be filed by date, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Subseries F: General Research
    - Badillo, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Managing the Budget in the Bloomberg Administration, circa 2003 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - City Almanac Ld Battein, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Archives Finding Aids, 2004-12 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Ed Koch and New York's Municipal Foreign Policy, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Request for 2003 Boston Globe, 2003-10-20 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Managing the Budget in the Bloomberg Administration 2001, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - The Sixties Revisited Pamphlets, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Subseries G: Scholarly Articles
    - Cities and Towns Article, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - "Follow the Money" Article, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - "American Nightmare" Article, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Annotated Scholarly Research, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - All for One or One for One, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Subseries H: Teaching
    - Minutes of the University Seminar on the City, 2006-11-06 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Soffer's Application for Position as Professor at the University of Southern Denmark, 2004-07-22 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Teaching Documentation, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Series II: Ridgway Project
  - Subseries A: Archival Manuscript Research
    - Box 46 MBR MSS Clippings Panama, Misc, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - MBR MSS Box 48 Folder 3 Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - MBR MSS Box 41 Sat Eve Post Srt, Corresp: Army Clipping Serv Reactions, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 1950's Testimonies, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Japanese Foreign Ministry Archives, 1990-11-12 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Eisenhower MSS Letters, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - MBR MSS Box 48 Clippings 1955-1959 Folder 1 Ed Ct on MBR's Views, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Great Projects/General Ridgway Interview/5-2-89, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - MBR MSS B1-23 Printouts (no 21-22), undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Ridgway MSS Box 47 Clippings on New Book, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Willis D. Crittenberger MSS USMHI Box C IADB, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Willis D. Crittenberger MSS USMHI Box E IADB, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - MBR MSS End of WWII, MSC/IADB, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - MBR MSS Box 42 Publications Soldier: Drafts, Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Bibliography Carlysle Finding Aid Ridgway MSS, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Ridgway to Marshall 28 Oct 1946 Ridgway MSS Box 8a, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript Research Notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Box 39 MBR MSS Speeches June 1955-1960, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - JMS/Brownell, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - MBR MSS Box 48 Folder 2 Editorial Criticizing MBR, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - McClure, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - MBR MSS Oral History, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Ridgway MSS Box 21 Korean War Misc official & personal papers, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Speech File MBR MSS Box 36 Mar-Aug 1954, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - MBR MSS Box 40 Speeches Jan 1959 May 1966, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Box 37 MBR MSS Speeches 1954-1955, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Ridgway Interview 1971 Transcripts, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Historical Materials in the Dwight D. Eisenhower Library, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Research Notecards, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - MBR MSS Box 36 Folder 2 Speeches August 53 - February 54, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - MBR MSS Box 34F Post Retirement Gen Files T-Z, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Box 34C Ridgway MSS Post Retirement "General Files H-L", undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - MBR MSS Box 34J, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - MBR MSS Box 34B Retirement Corresp A-G, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Ridgway MSS Post Retirement Box 34G, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ridgway MSS Box 34E Post Ret Corresp R-S, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Box 34D Ridgway MSS Post Retirement General Files M-Q, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ridgway MSS Box 34 Retirement Miscellany Box 34A Panels, McGovern Campaign 1955-1960, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - MBR MSS Box 42, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ruhr - Battle, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - MBR MSS, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - MBR MSS 1944-45 The Bulge, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Clay Blair, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - MBR MSS Box 5, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - McCoy, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Congressional Record-Senate 1945, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Military History Institute Papers, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Clay Blair Box 32, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Records of the US Electoral Mission, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - World War II Post Bulge 3 May 1945, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Heroism, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - After VEDAY, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Bulge-Gavin Corr re Hasbrouck, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Interlude July-Dec 44, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - MBR MSS Box 5A, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Varsity 1945 Mar 24-29, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Major General Frank R. McCoy Letter, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Archival Research Notecards, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - WHPCR, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence
    - Federal Court Correspondence, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Mail Correspondence, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Inter Office Memorandum Bilkent Universitesi, 1996-02-01 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1989-09-1994-04 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Trussell John B. Interview Permission Winton, Walter Correspondence, 1990-04-09 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The College of Staten Island Correspondence, 1993-05-20 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Mrs. Ridgway Interview Request Denied Letter, 1994-06-08 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Marion Letter, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Letter from Ridgway, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Dissertation Correspondence, 1989-01-13 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Subseries C: Drafts
    - Project Description and Proposal, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Prospectus Drafts, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Proposal for a Series of Essays on the Military and the Culture of Consumption, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Handwritten Draft and Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Comments on Drafts, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Letter from Manuscript Reader, 1991-07-08 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Chapter 5 Draft, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Paper Draft - Methods, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Work & Intellect Draft, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Subseries D: Interviews
    - Col John Trussell Interview Tapes with Jonathan Soffer, 1990-03-14 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Subseries E: Newspaper Research
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Scans, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - New York Times Newspaper Scans, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - The New York Review of Books July 15, 1993, 1993-07-15 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Blair Collections Bios of Thomas Some [illegible] Periodicals, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - New York Times, July 27, 1993, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Vietnam's 1972 Statement on P.O.W.'s: Triple the Total Hanoi Acknowledged, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Master Copy of "Pull-out, All-out, or Stand Fast in Vietnam?", undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Military Review April 1990, 1990-04 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Collier's Ad w Picture of MBR, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Subseries F: General Research
    - Current Task File, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Trip Planning, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - New Materials 7/91, 1991-07 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - NATO Notebook, 1990-02-07 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - US Army CS Ch 7, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - New BookGeneral Papers for later org, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - SCOR 1947, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Jonathan SofferThe University of Kansas Folder, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Trussell Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Huntington Lecture and Interviews, 1990-08-22 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Ch. 3 Latin America General, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Bibliography Presidential Libraries, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Latin Amer Chapter, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Thoughts on My Dissertation, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Historical Materials in the Dwight D. Eisenhower Library, 1989-12 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Bound Loose Leaf Papers, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Diplomatic History Spring 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bibliographic Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Book Notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Will of Peter I [A.D. 1725], undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Relations, 1947, Volume 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Diplomatic History: American Commitment to Germany, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Diplomatic History: NATO and the Korean War: A Context, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Cong Rec'd Jan 18, 1956 Volume 102 Pt 1 pg 755-77, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Foreign Relations, 1946, Volume 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Ch. 5 Europe General, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Warren R. Austin Papers, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Matthew Bunker Ridgway: Postwar Warrior 1946-1955, Dissertation Prospectus, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Ch. 2 UN Military Staff Ctte Sources, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Ridgway Project Biblio, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Photocopying Order, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Looseleaf Notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Goodpaster, Andrew Jackson, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - A Guide to the United States Army Military History Institute, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Book Requests, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Historical Materials in the John Fitzgerald Kennedy Library 1986, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - NATO Photocopies, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Paper Presented at "Ike's American Conference" Oct 1990, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Subseries G: Scholarly Articles
    - A Manifesto for Cyborgs by Donna Haraway Excerpt, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Warriors Future Present: The U.S. Military and the Postmodern* Soldier, 1988-07-20 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Information Over Time: A Semi-Technical Survey of European Military Change Before The Great War, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Entangling IllusionsJapanese and American Views of the Occupation by Carol Gluck, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Dules, Wedge, and the Sino-American Ambassadorial Talks, 1955-1957 by Qiang Zhai, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Heresy and Radical Politics, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Eisenhower's Latin American Economic Policy Aid: Promoting a "Way of Life", undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Troop Leadership At The Operational Level: The Eighth Army In Korea, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Race and Japanese Foreign Relations 1919-1945, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Scholarly Articles, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - "A Letter from W. E. B. Dubois to his Daughter Yolande" Article, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - The Quarterly Journal of Military History Volume 5, Number 1 Autumn 1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Ridgway Indo-China and Vietnam Articles, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Pretty Penny Ridgway, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - IndoChina, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Albert-(Am. Heritage) Article on MBR, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Prelude to the Geneva Conference, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - The National Association of Manufacturers and the Militarization of American Conservation, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Soldier's Return, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Mobilizing the World War II Economy, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Subseries H: Teaching
    - Columbia University GSAS Fellowships 91-92, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - History 531 Syllabus, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - History 100 Spring 1993 Final Exam (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Soffer Job Applications, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 1994 Resume (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Making a Bibliography, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Subject Proposal, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)